PACE DAVIS

707 Bishop Street · Smithville, TX 78957 · (512) 203-6498 · pacemdavis@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Certified Web Developer with diverse experience across multiple industries. Excellent history of developing and implementing databases and software to automate processes for clients, streamline daily operations, and reduce costs. Top strengths include website design, full-stack development, process improvement, automation, and problem-solving.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

| JavaScript | React | Express.js | HTML | |
|------------|-------|------------|------|--|
| MySQL | Redux | Node.js | CSS | |
| EXPERIENCE | | | | |

Austin Graffiti Removal

client relations as the main point of contact for customers

2018 – PresentOwner/Operator

Submitted proposals for work requests, oversaw company branding, updated website, and managed all

Austin, TX

- Grew business year-over-year by leveraging competitive advantages through google ads, proposal software, request forms, and social media presence
- Achieved revenue growth of 20% in 2020 by building new relationships with muralists and artists for expanding into a new sector of mural protection and revitalization
- Updated, modernized, and streamlined the proposal and accounting processes with automated software that eliminated the need for on-site visits, saving approximately 10-20 hours per month
- Developed company's WordPress site while managing social media and advertising campaigns
- Created web submission forms for work requests to automate the ordering process for clients

2014 – 2018 College Houses, Inc. Austin, TX

Facilities Director 2016 – 2018

- Oversaw maintenance and capital improvement projects for five cooperative housing facilities with 532 total residents while serving as the staff lead for the facilities board
- Developed and implemented a database for major capital improvement projects that included life-cycle maintenance tracking and enabled budgeting decisions to be made more efficiently
- Managed contracts for a \$1.1M walkway and balcony remodeling project, the largest capital improvement project of an existing structure in company history
- Co-created an online maintenance request form and digitized all structural and mechanical building plans to streamline each process
- Coordinated all major maintenance contracts with outside vendors and managed two suite remodel projects

Facilities Assistant 2014 – 2016

2014 Texas State Employees Union Austin, TX

Organizer

- Oversaw El Paso's state employees and all union members with the University of Texas at Austin while handling member issues, advocating for local and state members, and coordinating campaigns
- Facilitated the union's most successful university campaign, leading to a reversal on a \$10M call-center plan, a 25% increase in memberships at the University of Texas, and a 20% increase in memberships in the El Paso area

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin

Austin, TX

Bachelor of Arts in History (2012)

CERTIFICATIONS

Web Developer, Austin Coding Academy (2020)

Certificate from Harvard Business Extension Credentials of Readiness program (HBX CORe) (2018)